A Guide to the John A. Hartford Foundation records, Grants, Series 3 FA1218
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1908-1999; 3
  - Thomas Jefferson University: D. Balaban (RFP-172, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 330, Folder 2474)
  - University of Arkansas Medical School: J. McCormack (RFP-069, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 330, Folder 2475)
  - University of Arizona: P. Hurd (RFP-136, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 330, Folder 2476)
  - University of California, Davis: L. Stark (RFP-038, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 330, Folder 2477)
  - University of California, Los Angeles: L. Rubenstein (RFP-025, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 330, Folder 2478)
  - University of California San Diego: S. Crystal (RFP-031, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 331, Folder 2479)
  - University of California San Diego: D. Kripke (RFP-036, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 331, Folder 2480)
  - University of Cincinnati Medical Center: V. Warner (RFP-043, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 331, Folder 2481)
  - University of Colorado: C. Brazeau (RFP-077, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 331, Folder 2482)
  - University of Connecticut: R. Lusky (RFP-190, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 331, Folder 2483)
  - University of Florida: W. Hale (RFP-187, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 331, Folder 2484)
  - University of Florida: G. Caranasos (RFP-189, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 331, Folder 2485)
  - University of Georgia, College of Pharmacy: J. Cooper (RFP-033, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 331, Folder 2486)
  - University of Georgia Research Foundation L. Poon (RFP-034, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 331, Folder 2487)
  - University Hospital of Jacksonville: D. Covey (RFP-164, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 331, Folder 2488)
  - University of Illinois: M. Glasser (RFP-086, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 331, Folder 2489)
  - University of Illinois at Chicago: D. Dolinsky (RFP-085, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 332, Folder 2490)
  - University of Iowa: B. Thomas (RFP-040, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 332, Folder 2491)
  - University of Kansas: L. Redford (RFP-089, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 332, Folder 2492)
  - University of Louisville: K. Bellinger (RFP-152, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 332, Folder 2493)
  - University of Maryland: P. Lamy (RFP-068, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 332, Folder 2494)
  - University of Maryland: W. Allen (RFP-199, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 332, Folder 2495)
  - University of Miami: C. DeVito (RFP-178, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 332, Folder 2496)
  - University of Michigan: R. Beattie (RFP-080, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 332, Folder 2497)
  - University of Mississippi: B. Banahan (RFP-032, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 332, Folder 2498)
  - University of Missouri-Columbia: W. Patterson (RFP-005, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 333, Folder 2499)
  - University of Nevada: A. Greenhouse (RFP-084, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 333, Folder 2500)
  - University of North Carolina: J. Gagnon (RFP-094, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 333, Folder 2501)
  - University of Northern Colorado: M. Miller (RFP-110, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 333, Folder 2502)
  - University of Pennsylvania: D. Snook (RFP-072, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 333, Folder 2503)
  - University of Pennsylvania: K. Torbit (RFP-179, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 333, Folder 2504)
  - University of Pittsburgh: J. Nicholas (RFP-090, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 333, Folder 2505)
  - University of South Carolina: M. Dickson (RFP-125, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 333, Folder 2506)
  - University of South Florida: J. Moon (RFP-021, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 333, Folder 2507)
  - University of Southern California: J. Van Der Muelen (RFP-003, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 333, Folder 2508)
  - University of Southern Mississippi: P. Toom (RFP-149, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 334, Folder 2509)
  - University of Tennessee, College of Pharmacy: K. Roberts (RFP-113, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 334, Folder 2510)
  - University of Texas at Arlington: W. Nedderman (RFP-073, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 334, Folder 2511)
  - University of Texas at Arlington: P. Lecca (RFP-120, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 334, Folder 2512)
  - University of Texas Medical Branch at Galveston: S. Fisher (RFP-042, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 334, Folder 2513)
  - University of Texas at Houston: R. Opperman (RFP-051, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 334, Folder 2514)
  - University of Texas at San Antonio: R. Price (RFP-044, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 334, Folder 2515)
  - University of Texas at San Antonio: V. Lawrence (RFP-109, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 334, Folder 2516)
  - University of Utah: U. Riggs (RFP-139, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 334, Folder 2517)
  - University of Wisconsin, Madison: W. Vance (RFP-198, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 334, Folder 2518)
  - University of Wisconsin, Madison: B. Svarstad (RFP-183, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 335, Folder 2519)
  - University of Wyoming: S. Lundin (RFP-193, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 335, Folder 2520)
  - Utica College of Syracuse University: L. Baker (RFP-195, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 335, Folder 2521)
  - Ventura County Mental Health: E. Riddle (RFP-007, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 335, Folder 2522)
  - Veterans Administration (Vermont) M. Friedman (RFP-116, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 335, Folder 2523)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University: D. Snustad (RFP-146, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 335, Folder 2524)
  - Visiting Nurse Home Health Care: M. Adrian (RFP-124, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 335, Folder 2525)
  - Visiting Nurse Service of New York: E. Davis (RFP-156, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 336, Folder 2526)
  - Voluntary Hospitals of Iowa Home Care Services: J. Muenchow (RFP-081, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 336, Folder 2527)
  - West Mont Home Health Services: E. Henry (RFP-163, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 336, Folder 2528)
  - West Virginia University: A. Lucado (RFP-212, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 336, Folder 2529)
  - Wichita State University: M. Penner (RFP-020, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 336, Folder 2530)
  - Grant Appropriation Summaries, 1954-1960 (Box 336, Folder 2531)
  - Grant-Making Summaries, 1954-1960 (Box 336, Folder 2532-2533)
  - Grant Appropriation Summaries, 1961-1969 (Box 336, Folder 2534)
  - Grant-Making Summaries, 1961-1969 (Box 336, Folder 2535-2536)
  - Grant-Making Summaries, 1961-1969 (Box 337, Folder 2537-2542)
  - Grant Appropriation Summaries, 1970-1971 (Box 337, Folder 2543)
  - Grant-Making Summaries, 1970-1971 (Box 337, Folder 2544-2545)
  - Unsorted Early Grant Reports, 1960s-1970s (Box 338, Folder 2546-2551)
  - Unsorted Early Grant Reports, 1960s-1970s (Box 339, Folder 2552-2558)
  - Unsorted Early Grant Reports, 1960s-1970s (Box 340, Folder 2559-2564)
  - Hartford Fellowship Program: Committee on Grants, 1979 (Box 341, Folder 2565-2567)
  - Memos of Discussion on Fellowship Program, 1979 (Box 341, Folder 2568)
  - Fellowship Program Application Procedure, 1979-1980 (Box 341, Folder 2569)
  - Fellowship Program Administration, 1979-1980 (Box 341, Folder 2570)
  - Selection Procedures for Fellowships, 1979 (Box 341, Folder 2571)
  - Fellowship Selection Committee Members, 1979-1980 (Box 341, Folder 2572)
  - Letter about Biomedical Research Impact, 1979 (Box 341, Folder 2573)
  - Medical Research Grant Evaluation, 1979 (Box 341, Folder 2574)
  - Fellowship Program Evaluation, 1980-1981 (Box 341, Folder 2575)
  - Letter about SRI and Energy Grants, circa 1980 (Box 341, Folder 2576)
  - Program Officer Job Description (Fellowship Program), 1979 (Box 341, Folder 2577)
  - Planning for First Fellows Annual Meeting, 1980 (Box 341, Folder 2578)
  - Fellowship Organization Working File, 1979 (Box 341, Folder 2579)
  - Fellowship Program Advisory Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 341, Folder 2580)
  - Fellows Selection, 1980-1981 (Box 341, Folder 2581)
  - Fellowships at Other Institutions, 1980-1981 (Box 341, Folder 2582)
  - Annual Fellows Conference Planning, 1981 (Box 342, Folder 2583)
  - Fellowship Policy Concerns, 1981 (Box 342, Folder 2584)
  - Fellowship Candidates, 1980 (Box 342, Folder 2585)
  - Fellowship Application and Promotional Materials, 1984-1986 (Box 342, Folder 2586)
  - Fellowship Program Planning, 1979-1980 (Box 342, Folder 2587)
  - Fellowship Program Timetable, 1979 (Box 342, Folder 2588)
  - Selection Committee and Budget, 1980 (Box 342, Folder 2589)
  - Selection Committee Meeting Planning, 1980 (Box 342, Folder 2590)
  - Selection Committee Procedures, 1980 (Box 342, Folder 2591)
  - Selection Committee member Robert Canfield, 1980 (Box 342, Folder 2592)
  - Selection Committee member Attallah Kappas, 1980 (Box 342, Folder 2593)
  - Selection Committee member David Kipnis, 1980 (Box 342, Folder 2594)
  - Selection Committee member Alfred Maumenee, 1980 (Box 342, Folder 2595)
  - Selection Committee member Barbara McNeil, 1980 (Box 342, Folder 2596)
  - Selection Committee member Thomas Merigan, 1980 (Box 342, Folder 2597)
  - Photographs of 1980 Hartford Fellows (Box 342, Folder 2598)
  - Selection Committee Members, 1980 (Box 342, Folder 2599)
  - Possible Members of Selection Committee, 1979 (Box 342, Folder 2600)
  - Information for Selection Committee, 1979 (Box 342, Folder 2601)
  - Correspondence on Fellowship Program, 1979 (Box 343, Folder 2602)
  - Fellowship Program meeting with attorney Barbara Robinson, 13-Jul-79 (Box 343, Folder 2603)
  - Survey of other fellowship programs, 1979 (Box 343, Folder 2604)
  - Internal Revenue Service Correspondence on Fellowship Program, 1979-1980 (Box 343, Folder 2605)
  - Medical research reports, 1978-1979 (Box 343, Folder 2606)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges Directory, 1979 (Box 343, Folder 2607)
  - Fellowship Timetables, 1979-1980 (Box 343, Folder 2608)
  - Fellowship Program Responsibilities, 1979-1980 (Box 343, Folder 2609)
  - Fellowship Selection Committee Meeting, Sep-81 (Box 343, Folder 2610)
  - Fellowship Acceptance Letters, 1982 (Box 343, Folder 2611)
  - Selection Committee Honoraria, 1981 (Box 343, Folder 2612)
  - Applicants for Fellowships, 1980 (Box 343, Folder 2613)
  - Selection Committee Correspondence, 1980 (Box 343, Folder 2614)
  - Foundation Correspondence on Fellowships, 1980 (Box 343, Folder 2615)
  - Fellowship Selection Committee Meetings, 1979-1980 (Box 344, Folder 2616)
  - Fellowship Rankings, 1980 (Box 344, Folder 2617)
  - Fellowship Acceptance Letters, 1980 (Box 344, Folder 2618)
  - Fellowship Alternate Letters, 1980 (Box 344, Folder 2618)
  - Fellowship Declinations Letters, 1980 (Box 344, Folder 2620)
  - National Health Research Policy Letters, 1980 (Box 344, Folder 2621)
  - Selection Committee Trustee Members, 1980 (Box 344, Folder 2622)
  - Application reviews by Kappas, 1980 (Box 344, Folder 2623)
  - Application reviews by Kipnis, 1980 (Box 344, Folder 2624)
  - Application reviews by Maumenee, 1980 (Box 344, Folder 2625)
  - Application reviews by McNeil, 1980 (Box 344, Folder 2626)
  - Application reviews by Merigan, 1980 (Box 344, Folder 2627)
  - Fellowship Program Evaluation File, 1908-1981 (Box 344, Folder 2628)
  - Rand Corporation Evaluation of Fellowship Program, 1982-1983 (Box 344, Folder 2629)
  - Fellowship Applicants, 1981 (Box 345, Folder 2630)
  - Application Reviewer Assignments and Evaluations, 1980-1981 (Box 345, Folder 2631)
  - Applicant Rankings, 1981 (Box 345, Folder 2632)
  - Fellows and Alternates, 1981 (Box 345, Folder 2633)
  - Fellowship Acceptance Letters, 1981 (Box 345, Folder 2634)
  - Fellowship Alternate Letters, 1981 (Box 345, Folder 2635)
  - Fellowship Declination Letters, 1981 (Box 345, Folder 2636)
  - Fellowship Applicants, 1982 (Box 345, Folder 2637)
  - Fellowship Declination Letters, 1982 (Box 345, Folder 2638)
  - Selection Committee Honoraria and Expenses, 1982-1983 (Box 345, Folder 2639)
  - Selection Committee: Robert Canfield, 1979-1986 (Box 345, Folder 2640)
  - Selection Committee: Bernard Fields, 1985-1986 (Box 345, Folder 2641)
  - Selection Committee: Dan Foster, 1983-1986 (Box 345, Folder 2642)
  - Selection Committee: Attalah Kappas, 1979-1986 (Box 345, Folder 2643)
  - Selection Committee: David Kipnis, 1979-1986 (Box 345, Folder 2644)
  - Selection Committee: Alfred Maumenee, 1979-1982 (Box 345, Folder 2645)
  - Selection Committee: Barbara McNeil, 1979-1986 (Box 345, Folder 2646)
  - Selection Committee: Thomas Merigan, 1979-1986 (Box 345, Folder 2647)
  - Selection Committee: John Oates, 1983-1986 (Box 346, Folder 2648)
  - Selection Committee: Bill Paul, 1983 (Box 346, Folder 2649)
  - Selection Committee: Leon Rosenberg, 1979-1985 (Box 346, Folder 2650)
  - Selection Committee: Richard Stiehm, 1983-1986 (Box 346, Folder 2651)
  - Selection Committee: Samuel Wells, 1985-1986 (Box 346, Folder 2652)
  - Potential Selection Committee Member: Lewis Thomas, 1979 (Box 346, Folder 2653)
  - Blank Application Forms, 1980-1981 (Box 346, Folder 2654)
  - Research on Matching Grants for Staff, 1980 (Box 346, Folder 2655)
  - Robyn Dietz Files: Selection Committee Meeting Set-Up, 1983 (Box 346, Folder 2656)
  - Robyn Dietz Files: Selection Committee Meeting Set-Up, 1984 (Box 346, Folder 2657)
  - Robyn Dietz Files: Selection Committee Meeting Set-Up, 1985 (Box 346, Folder 2658)
  - Robyn Dietz Files: Selection Committee Meeting Set-Up, 1986 (Box 346, Folder 2659)
  - Robyn Dietz Files: Chronological File, 1984-1986 (Box 347, Folder 2660-2663)
  - Robyn Dietz Files: Selection Committee CVs, 1980s (Box 347, Folder 2664)
  - Robyn Dietz Files: Lists of Fellows, 1983-1985 (Box 347, Folder 2665)
  - Robyn Dietz Files: Applications Declined, 1985-1986 (Box 348, Folder 2666)
  - Robyn Dietz Files: Letters to Deans of Declined Applications, 1985-1986 (Box 348, Folder 2667)
  - Parkland Memorial Hospital: J. Hayman (RFP-105, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 348, Folder 2668)
  - Pennsylvania State University: W. Moir (RFP-045, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 348, Folder 2669)
  - Philadelphia College of Pharmacy: P. Gierbino (RFP-052, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 348, Folder 2670)
  - Pontiac Osteopathic Hospital: R. Margoles (RFP-170, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 348, Folder 2671)
  - Portland VA Medical Center: J. Stilwell (RFP-029, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 348, Folder 2672)
  - Research Foundation of the State University of New York: R. Teliska (RFP-009, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 348, Folder 2673)
  - Roanoke Valley Adult Day Center: L. Oakes (RFP-017, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 348, Folder 2674)
  - Rocky Knoll Health Care Facility: J. Wethington (RFP-147, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 348, Folder 2675)
  - Rocky Mountain Drug Consultation Center: L. Golightly (RFP-066, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 348, Folder 2676)
  - Rush-Presbyterian-St. Luke's Medical Center: J. Fawcett (RFP-181, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 348, Folder 2677)
  - Rutgers University: M. Smith (RFP-142, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 349, Folder 2678)
  - San Francisco Department of Public Health D. Werdegar (RFP-196, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 349, Folder 2679)
  - Serve Our Seniors, Inc.: J. Barry (RFP-054, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 349, Folder 2680)
  - South Bay Free Clinic: R. Oksas (RFP-071, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 349, Folder 2681)
  - South Dakota State University: P. Meyer (RFP-204, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 349, Folder 2682)
  - South Dakota State University: B. Repschlaeger (RFP-207, declined), 1985-1986 (Box 349, Folder 2683)